Magnitude of Change Associated with Breakthrough
Hello, Mike Harry, and welcome back again. Where we're going to be looking at
benchmarking. In specific, some actual benchmarks of data that has been collected.
A little bit about how to do that benchmarking. Well, let's begin.
First, we have our Sigma scale showing out here, as 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 Sigma.
Second column is defects per million opportunity.
And the next column is the magnitude of change from the previous DPMO.
And of course, the associated cost of quality recognizing that's typical.
So, you can see, for example, at 3 Sigma,
we would have 66,807 defects per million opportunities.
Now, that represents a 5X change over the previous benchmark,
308,538 defects per million opportunities.
In other words, as I move from 2 to 3 Sigma capability,
there is a five times difference. And of course, that's rounded.
The typical cost of quality associated with 3 Sigma, is about 30% of sales.
Now, we can see that best in class is running at about
4-1/2 Sigma and world-class at around 5 Sigma.
Of course, if we're Six Sigma we’re about less than 1%, in terms of cost of quality.
There's a 68 times improvement over 5 Sigma.
We’re running 3.4 defects per million opportunities.
Thank you for choosing SSMI.